제작 - 네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24
위스콘신주 포인트 플레이스
Point Place, Wisconsin
1977년 1월 13일
January 13th, 1977
목요일 오후
Thursday Afternoon
에릭네 지하실
Eric Forman's Basement
좋아, 간단해
학교 끝나고 출발하면
All right, this is no sweat.
If we leave right after school...
재키네 스키 별장에 6시쯤
도착할 수 있을 거야
we should make it to
Jackie's ski cabin by, like, 6:00.
야, 빨리 가고 싶다
내가 제일 좋아하는 곳이지
Man, I can't wait.
A trip to my favorite place.
여기 빼고 제일
Anywhere but here.
알파인 밸리에 가면 소년이 도나랑
진한 키스를 할 찬스가 많을 거야
And I'm betting that
alpine Valley is gonna give the kid...
many make-out opportunities
with Donna this weekend.
소년은 불타오르고 있어
The kid is in.
왜 자꾸 "소년" 이란
말을 하는 거야?
What's with the whole "kid" thing?
멋있으니까
It's cool.
멋있지 않아?
It's not cool?
멋 없어. 촌스러
Not cool. Dorky.
체육관 뒤에서 팸 메이시랑
키스한 사람이 누구게?
Guess who made out with
Pam Macy behind the gym?
세상 사람 다
Everyone.
아니야!
No!
나야!
Me!
켈소, 체육관 뒤에서
노는 애들 많잖아
Kelso, a lot of people
hang out behind the gym.
맞아, 그래서 더 대단하다는 거 아냐
다들 봤거든
Yeah, that's what's so great about it.
Everybody saw it!
정말 잘했어, 친구
That's great, man.
그래, 이제 다들 재키한테
이를 거 아냐, 이 멍청아
Yeah. Because now everybody
can tell Jackie, you moron.
맞아, 그럼 걔가 널 죽이려고 할 거고
우린 걔네 별장에 못 간단 말야
Then she's gonna dump you
and we won't be able to go up...
- to her ski cabin.
- She's never gonna find out.
재키는 모를 거야
이 나쁜 놈, 마이클
넌 더럽고 불결한 개야!
You are a dog, Michael,
a dirty, dirty dog!
- 내가 뭘 어쨌다고?
- 팸 메이시랑 키스했잖아
- What did I do?
- You kissed Pam Macy.
난 널 믿었는데, 인제 내 친구들이
전부 날 비웃고 있어
I trusted you, Michael, and now
all my friends are laughing at me.
난 이제 3층 화장실에
얼굴도 못 내밀게 생겼어
I can't even show my face
in the third floor bathroom anymore.
그 화장실 정말 좋단 말야
And that's the cool bathroom.
- 그치만, 난
- 아니, 마이클. 우린 끝이야
- But, I...
- No, Michael. We're through.
좋아, 니가 원하는 게
그거라면, 끝내
Okay. If that's the way you want it,
we're through.
월요일 날 스키 여행에서
돌아오면, 그때 끝내자
And Monday, when we get back
from that ski trip, it's over.
아냐, 마이클
아냐, 아냐, 아냐
No, Michael, no.
넌 이번 주말에 스키 못 타
You won't be skiing this weekend.
아주 잘 났다, 재키
That's just great, Jackie.
어디 스키 여행 취소해서
친구들 실망시켜봐
Cancel the ski trip
and disappoint all our friends.
아냐, 아냐
우리끼리는 갈 거야
No. We are still going.
얘들은 나 없이는 안 갈껄?
They're surely not going
without me.
그치, 얘들아?
Right, guys?
아 참, 우리 부모님은 안가고
우리끼리만 갈 거란 얘기 했나?
And did I mention
my parents are not coming...
so it'll be just us?
그럼, 월요일날 보자!
So, we'll see you Monday!
토퍼 그레이스 (에릭 포먼)
밀라 커니스 (재키 벅하트)
애쉬튼 커쳐 (마이클 켈소)
대니 메스털슨 (스티븐 하이드)
로라 프레폰 (도나 핀씨오티)
윌머 발더라마 (페즈)
데브라 조 러프 (키티 포먼)
커트우드 스미스 (레드 포먼)
타냐 로버츠 (미지 핀씨오티)
돈 스탁 (밥 핀씨오티)
That '70s Show 자막팀
영문자막 : 김민경(paramount@nate)
싱크수정, 번역 : 김현정(fuchs@nate)
That '70s Show 자막팀
영문자막 : 김민경(paramount@nate)
싱크수정 : 김현정(fuchs@nate)
1x13 Ski Trip
Jan 17, 1999 on FOX
그래, 에릭은 주말동안
집에 없으니까
So, Eric's going away
for the weekend.
집이 온통 우리 차지겠군
Whole house to ourselves.
그게 뭘 의미하는지 알겠어?
You know what that means?
TV 앞에서 저녁 먹을 수 있죠
Dinner in front of the TV.
아냐
No.
이 짐승
You dog.
에릭
Now, Eric,
you're gonna be driving in snow...
네 눈길 운전을 대비해서
차량용 비상 물품함을 준비해 뒀다
비상시를 대비해서 말이야
so I'll put together
an emergency roadside kit for you.
In case you run into trouble.
고맙습니다
잘 됐네요
Okay, that'd be great.
준비에 따라 결과가
달라지는 법이다
Preparation makes all the difference,
Eric. Take kitty litter.
고양이 깔짚을 꼭 챙겨라
모래나 겨 등 고양이집 바닥에 까는 것
고양이 깔짚이 얼마나 많이
나를 곤경에서 구했는지 모를 거다
I can't tell you how many times
kitty litter got me out of a tight spot,
70년대 들어서 언젠가는...
I remember one time in the '70s,
오, 에릭
Oh, my God, Eric.
엥? 비상 조명탄이잖아
Oh. It's a road flare.
비상 조명탄이 네 생명을
구할 수도 있단다
A road flare can save your life,
"비상 조명탄이 네 생명을
구할 수도 있다" 니까
I said, "a road flare
can save your life."
네? 맞아요. 그럼요
비상 조명탄..
What? Check. Great.
Road flare. Right.
오늘 학교에서 별일 없었니?
Okay, now, good.
How was school today?
우리 체육선생님이신
윌슨 코치님 아시죠?
Okay, you know my PE Teacher,
Coach Wilson?
그 코치 입가에 지저분한
딱지 같은 게 있더라구요
He had this crusty stuff
in the corner of his lip.
그래서 켈소가 코치한테
So Kelso says to him...
"코치님, 거기 그 지저분한 거
좀 떼세요...."
"Coach, check out
that crusty stuff..."
지난주에 그 코치가...
Last week, the coach,,,,
아빠?
Dad?
아빠, 듣고 계시는 거예요?
Dad, are you even listening?
당연히 듣고 있지
Of course I'm listening.
내 생각엔 말이다?
And you know what I'm hearing?
넌 최선을 다해야 돼
You need to buckle down.
학교생활이 얼마나 중요한지는
내가 수도 없이 말했을 거다
I've told you over and over again
that school is so important.
네가 지금 하는 거에 따라서...
What you do now determines,,,,
여보, 거기 너무 좋아요
Red, that is so good.
바로 거기에요
Right there.
거기는 몇년동안
손길 한번 안 갔어요
That hasn't been touched in years.
도나, 내가 더블사이즈 슬리핑 백
가져 왔어. 알지?
Donna, man, I brought
my double sleeping bag. You know?
잘 됐다, 에릭이랑 내가
빌려써도 되지?
Great. Can Eric and I borrow it?
하이드, 니가 계속
삽질하는 걸 보니까
Hyde, watching you
fail over and over...
찰리 브라운하고 축구공이 생각나
만화 "스누피"의 주인공
it is like Charlie Brown
and the football.
맞다, 그래. 내가 못 잡았네
Yeah, man, I just don't get it.
맞아, 왜냐면 이미 에릭이
쥐고 있으니까
No, because Eric already has it.
미안
Hey.
안녕, 켈소
Hey, Kelso.
야, 네가 맘 상하지 않았음 좋겠다
Look, I just wanna make sure
we're cool.
이번 주말은 나랑 도나한테
정말 중요하거든
'Cause this weekend is, like,
really important for me and Donna.
So, thanks for understanding.
이해해 줘서 고맙다
그래, 나도 이해해
Yeah. I understand.
우리가 더 이상
친구가 아니란 걸 말야
I understand that
we're not friends anymore.
야, 이건 전부
네가 자초한 일이야
Look, man, you brought
this on yourself.
그래, 그렇지만 그 까짓건
나만 따 당할 이유는 못 돼
I know I did,
but that's no reason for me to suffer.
아냐, 그만한 이유가 또 어딨냐?
No, that is a great reason
for you to suffer.
- 나 간다
- 좋아, 가. 내가 신경이나 쓰나 봐라
- I'm going.
- Fine. Go. See if I care.
그러지 마, 에릭
이러면 안 되지
Come on, Eric. Come on, man.
- 자, 차량용 비상 물품함이다
- 고양이 깔짚요?
Here's your emergency
roadside kit. / Kitty litter?
아, 고양이 깔짚요, 맞다
Kitty litter. Right.
얘야, 가방 안에
샌드위치를 좀 넣어뒀다
Honey, I put some sandwiches
in your duffel bag.
무슨 오레가노를 저렇게 많이 가져가니?
향신료, 마리화나랑 비슷하게 생겼음
Now why do you need
such a big bag of oregano?
도나가 이태리계라서요?
Donna's Italian.
그래, 따뜻하게 입고
Okay, stay warm.
아, 이제야 뭔지 알았다
Okay, I see what's going on.
니들 진짜 스키타러
가는 거 아니지?
You're not really going skiing.
이거 다 그냥 나 열받게
하려는 쇼지?
This is all just a gag. You're
trying to get me all worked up...
그러다 "장난이었어, 친구"
이러려고?
so you can go,
"Just kidding, buddy! "
완전히 속았었네
Yeah, you got me.
멋진 속임수였어
That's a nice burn.
그러게
It sure is.
잘 있어
Bye-bye.
가는 거 아니에요
He's not going.
돌아올 거예요
He'll be back.
잠깐만 기다려 보세요
저기를 돌아서 올 거예요
Any second now. He's probably
just going around the block.
정말 못 당하겠다니까요
완전히 속았었어요
I gotta hand it to him,
he got me there.
정말 대단한 속임수예요
That's a major burn.
정말요
Yup.
저깄어요, 저럴 줄 알았다니까요!
There he is. I knew it!
엥, 에릭이 아니네
No, that's not him.
나 눈 처음 봐
I have never seen snow before.
너무 아름다워
It is so beautiful.
이번 여행에서 가장 좋은 게
뭔지 아니?
Do you know what
the best part of this whole trip is?
마이클이 여기 없다는 거야
That Michael is not here.
여기 있었음 모피 장식 코트 입은
내 모습이 귀엽다는 소리나 했겠지
He'd just be sitting here telling me
how cute I look in my fur-trimmed coat.
내가 귀여운 건 나도 아니까
굳이 걔가 필요 없어
I know I look cute.
I don't need him here for that.
야, 포먼. 너희 아빠가 주신
이 잡동사니는 다 뭐냐?
Forman, man, what's
all this crap that Red gave you?
나도 몰라. 고양이 깔짚에
완전히 빠지셨다니까
I don't know.
He's obsessed with kitty litter.
아무래도 미쳐가시는 게
아닌가 몰라
I think he might be going insane.
장난 아닌데?
Far out.
대체 어떻게 된 거야?
What the hell was that?
몰라. 길에 얼음이 있었나 봐
I don't know.
I guess we hit some ice.
젠장, 차가 빠져버렸어
Great, we're stuck.
이것 봐!
내가 처음 만든 눈덩이야
Look, I made my first snowball.
나 눈을 너무 사랑하나 봐
내 손가락이 기쁨으로 무감각해졌어
I love snow so much,
my fingers are numb with joy.
동상걸린 거야, 페즈
That's frostbite, Fez.
감히 어딜!
How rude.
난 너희 흰둥이들의
겨울을 증오해
I hate your white man's winter.
차에 타, 페즈
Get in the car, Fez.
에릭, 어떻게 해 봐
Eric, do something.
맞아, 삽질 그만하고
어떻게 좀 해봐
Yeah, man, stop goofing around.
얼어 죽겠네
It's freezing.
정말 끔찍해
우린 다 죽을 거야
This is awful.
We're all going to die...
그리고 난 마이클을 사랑해
and I love Michael.
닥쳐!
Shut up!
좋아, 생각해 봐, 에릭
생각해 봐
Okay, think, Eric, think.
고양이 깔집을 왜 주셨을까?
Why kitty litter?
접착제를 사용해라, 에릭
Use the gum, Eric,
아빠? 여기서 뭐 하시는 거예요?
Dad? What're you doing here?
난 여기 있는 게 아니라
네가 날 상상하고 있는 거다
I'm not here,
You're imagining me,
자, 누가 미쳤다고?
이 입만 살은 녀석아!
Now who's insane,
Mr, Smartmouth?
제가 미쳤었나 봐요
I guess I am.
접착제로 초를 깡통에 붙여라
Use the gum to stick
the candle in the can,
촛불에 깡통이 뜨거워지면
그걸로 타이어 뒤의 눈을 녹이거라
The candle heats the can,
which melts the snow behind the tire,
그 다음 고양이 깔집을 부어서
마찰이 생기게 해
Then pour on the kitty litter
for traction,
자, 할 수 있겠냐?
Now you think you can handle that?
- 네, 아버지
- 잘 됐구나
- Yes, sir.
- Good,
날 또 불러냈다간
좋지 못할 테니까 말이다
Because you don't want
me back out here,
내가 네 상상일 뿐 일지는 몰라도
I may be a figment of
your imagination,,,
엉덩이 시렵단 말이다
I'm still freezing my ass off.
마이클, 너 여기서 뭐하니?
Michael, what are you
doing down here?
그거 아세요?
You know what?
에릭이 정말 가버린 것 같아요
I think Eric actually went.
나쁜 자식
What a jerk.
재키네 별장에 가서
직접 얘기하지 그러니?
Why don't you just go to
Jackie's cabin and talk to him?
못 가요, 차가 없거든요
I can't, I don't have a car.
게다가, 제가 팸 메이시랑 키스해서
재키가 절 영원히 증오할 거예요
Besides, Jackie hates me forever
'cause I kissed Pam Macy.
있지, 아저씨랑 내가 연애할 때
You know, when Mr. Forman
and I were dating...
나도 그 이가 어떤 여자애랑
키스하는 걸 봤는데도
I saw him kissing a girl
in a movie theater once...
그 이를 용서했단다
and I forgave him.
딴 여자랑 키스했는데도
용서하셨다구요?
You forgave him for kissing
another girl?
그렇다니까
Yes, sir.
그건 키스였다기 보다는
I mean it wasn't so much kissing...
애무같은 거였어
as it was a groping...
질척하고, 할퀴고
물어뜯는 악몽같은 거였지
sloppy, pawing,
nibbling nightmare.
그런데도 용서하셨구요
But you forgave him.
그래. 그 자식을 용서했어
Yeah. I forgave the bastard.
멋져요!
Cool!
좋아, 초?
됐고
Okay. Candles, check.
포도주?
됐고
Chianti, check.
너트 믹스?
됐어
Fancy nut mix, check.
- 어때, 우리 아리따운 아가씨?
- 헛소리 하지 말아요
- And how's my pretty lady?
- You are so full of crap.
괜찮니?
Hello there.
세워주셔서 고마워요
Thanks for stopping.
알파인 밸리까지
데려다 주실 수 있으세요?
Are you going all the way
to alpine Valley?
너 가는 곳이면 어디든 간단다
I'm going wherever you're going.
우와, 정말 다행이네요
Wow. That's lucky.
어디 말해보렴
So tell me, did it hurt?
아팠니?
뭐가요?
What?
하늘나라에서 떨어질 때 말이다
When you fell down from heaven.
아뇨, 괜찮아요
No, I'm fine.
좋았어, 도착했다!
All right, we made it!
제때 도착해서 다행이다
폭풍이 사나워지고 있었거든
Yeah, just in time.
That storm was getting nasty.
나 너무 추워
I am so cold.
눈이 내 남자다움을
앗아가 버렸어
The snow has stolen my manhood.
침실이 한개 밖에 없어
There's only one bedroom.
원래 나랑 마이클이 쓰려고 했는데
우리 사랑이...
It was gonna be for Michael and I,
but since our love is...
끝나 버렸으니까
Dead...
너희 둘이 써도 돼
you two should take it.
좋아
All right. Want to go
check out our room?
- 우리 방 보러 갈래?
- 당연하지
Definitely.
너희들 어디 가는 거야?
다 같이 놀기로...
Where are you guys going?
I thought we were gonna hang the...
나 얼어 죽어
I am freezing.
우리 나라는 겨울에도
영상 21도란 말야
The winter in my country
is 70 degrees.
얼어 죽지 않으려면
서로 꼭 껴안아야 돼
We must hold each other
for warmth.
만지지 마!
Stop touching me!
그치만 나 죽는단 말야!
But I am going to die!
좋아, 페즈, 오, 아마레또가 있구나
아몬드 맛 이태리 술. 28도
Okay, Fez, amaretto.
이게 네 몸을
따뜻하게 해줄 거야
You know what, man?
This'll warm you right up.
한 모금 마셔봐
Take a sip of that.
얌, 술 캔디구나
Yum, liquid candy.
여보, 20년이나 지난 얘기잖아
Kitty, you're talking about something
that happened over 20 years ago.
당신은 영화보러 가서는
하나님과 사람들 보는 데서
And there you were at the movies,
in front of God and everybody...
말대가리 린 타일러를
무슨 아이스 바처럼 할짝거렸죠
slurping on horse face Lyn Taylor
like she was a Popsicle.
여보 / 대갈 공주에, 헤픈
말대가리 아이스 바처럼요
- Kitty...
- A big, easy, horse-faced Popsicle.
말대가리라니?
Horse face?
미스 위스콘신 대회 준우승자였어
She was a runner-up
in the Miss Wisconsin pageant.
하긴 우승을 못했지
Which she lost because she
was such a horse face.
말대가리였으니까
버거 고마워요
Thanks for the burger.
모자도요
And the hat.
그 웃는 모습이 맘에 드는걸
I just like to see that smile.
네 친구 에릭 때문에
풀이 죽어 있나 보구나
You seem kinda down
about your friend Eric.
맞아요
Yeah.
그게.. 있죠
걘 항상 제 곁에 있어 줬어요
It's just, you know,
he's always been there for me.
사람들이 저를 멍청이라고 부를 때도
Like when people used to
call me dumb...
"네 생각처럼 그렇게 멍청하진 않아"
라고 말해 주곤 했어요
he'd say, "He's not as dumb
as you think."
사람들은 그 얘기를 꺼려하지만
People don't like to talk about it...
그래도 남자들끼리의 관계라는 게
아주 특별하죠, 안 그래요?
but guy-to-guy relationships
are pretty special, you know?
세상에서 가장
아름다운 것일 수도 있지
They can be the most
beautiful thing in the world.
저도 제가 왜 이러는지 모르겠어요
이건 그냥 무슨..
I don't know why I do this stuff.
It's just, like...
억제할 수 없는 강한 충동 같아요
I get these urges,
you know, and I can't control them.
내가 그 마음을
컨트리송으로 만들었지
Shoot, I wrote that country song.
♪ 난 속아왔어요 ♪
"When Will I Be Loved" by Linda Ronstadt
♪ I've been cheated ♪
♪ 학대당한 거죠 ♪
♪ Been mistreated ♪
♪ 난 언제쯤 사랑받을 수 있을까요? ♪
♪ When will I be loved ♪
저건 그냥 재키가 우는 걸 거야
That's probably just Jackie crying.
맞아
Yeah.
안 되겠다. 너무 심하잖아
All right, that's too much.
제발 나가서
저 레코드 좀 꺼줄래?
Can you please go out there
and break that record?
무슨 일이야?
What's going on?
"스파이 대 스파이" 인데
웃겨 죽겠어
"Spy vs. Spy," man,
they kill me.
너 말고 얘
No, with her.
좀 심란한가 보네
She seems upset or something.
그런데, 페즈는 어디 갔어?
Okay, look, where's Fez?
페즈?
아마레또 한병을 아작내더니
Fez? He killed that
entire bottle of amaretto...
눈사람 만들어야 된다면서 뛰쳐 나갔어
Snow Angel: 눈밭에 쓰러져서 만드는 실루엣
and then he ran outside,
saying he had to make a snow angel.
근데 속옷만 입고 나갔어
But he was in his underwear.
야, 페즈를 찾아오던가
아님 재키를 달래던가 해
Look, you either need to
go get Fez or console Jackie.
알았어, 내가 도나를 맡을게
All right, I'll take Donna.
- 재키 말야
- 맞다, 재키 그래
- Jackie.
- Yeah. Jackie.
괜찮아
Okay.
그래, 네가 슬픈 거 알아
Yeah, okay, I can see you're upset.
자 이제, 들어봐, 알았지?
Now, listen, all right?
위로가 될지 모르겠는데
If it's any consolation...
팸 메이시는 아무하고나 다 해
Pam Macy would give it up
to anybody.
우리 단 둘 뿐인데 어때?
What do you know?
We're all alone.
하이드, 너 진짜 나쁘다, 알아?
God, Hyde, you can be such a jerk,
you know that?
- 왜 이래, 실수였어
- 일부러 그랬잖아
- Come on, I'm just goofing around.
- No, you're not.
난 여기 에릭이랑 온 거야, 알았어?
Look, I'm up here with Eric.
All right?
- 네가 아니란 말야
- 알아, 됐어? 안다고
- Get it? Not you.
- I know, okay?
너 내가 친구 애인이나 꼬시는
그런 놈으로 보이냐?
Look, do you think I like hitting
on my best friend's girlfriend?
아니야
I don't.
근데 널 보고 있으면
그게, 널 보고 있으면..
But I look at you,
I mean, look at you.
나도 어쩔 수 없어
I can't help it.
좀 낫네
You better.
이제 확실히 알겠어요
It's so clear to me now.
난 사람들을 내 성적 노리개로
이용하고 다녀선 안 돼요
I can't just go around using
people as my sexual playthings.
무슨 말인지 아시죠, 아저씨?
You know what I mean, Gus?
왜냐면 사람들의 감정이
성적 충동보다 훨씬 중요하니까요
'Cause people's feelings
are way more important...
than those sexual urges.
너 정말 착하구나, 얘야
You're good people, son.
아저씨도요
You, too, man.
여기서 내리거라
This is where you get off.
그리고 한가지 더
다음 번엔 버스를 타라
And one more thing. Next time,
take a bus. You're too pretty to hitch.
넌 히치 하이킹하기엔 너무 예뻐
고마워요, 아저씨
Thanks, man.
잘가요, 아저씨
Bye, Gus.
페즈!
Fez!
어이, 친구!
Hey, man.
- 켈소, 어떻게 왔어?
- 정말 착한 아저씨가 태워줬어
- Kelso. You're here.
- Yeah. I got a ride with the nicest guy.
야, 여기까지 오면서
정말 많이 생각해 봤는데 말야
Listen, I had a lot of time
to think on the way up here.
미안해
And, I'm sorry.
그래, 나도 미안해
Yeah, I'm sorry.
널 두고 여기 오는 게 아니었어
I should never have come up here
without you, man.
난 겨울 요정이다
I am a winter nymph.
난 눈을 사랑해
I love the snow.
미국 만세!
Hooray america!
마이클!
Michael!
나랑 같이 있으려고 눈보라를 뚫고
여기까지 걸어 왔구나, 그렇지, 마이클?
You walked all the way here in a
driving snowstorm just to be with me...
didn't you, Michael?
팸 메이시랑 다시는
그 짓 안할 거지, 그렇지?
And you would never ever do
that for Pam Macy, would you?
안 할걸?
No?
- 내 사랑
- 당연하지
- Lover.
- You know it.
둘중 아무나
얘 바지 좀 입혀줄래?
Could one of you guys
put his pants on?
여보, 당신이 그 여자 문제만
가지고 이럴 리가 없어
Kitty, this can't just be
about me and Lyn Taylor.
- 진짜 문제가 뭐야?
- 좋아요
- What's really bothering you?
- Okay.
왜 난 아니었는지 알고 싶어요
I just want to know why not me?
당신이 뭐가 아니라는 거야?
당신이랑 결혼했잖아
Why not you what? I married you.
그래요, 그치만 나랑
데이트할 땐 그냥 앉아서
Yeah, but when we were dating,
you just sat there.
공손하게 내 손만
잡고 있었다구요
You held my hand politely.
나도 공공장소에서의 격정적인 행위를
즐길지도 모른다는 생각은 안 해봤어요?
Didn't you think that I might
enjoy a passionate manhandling...
in a public place?
난 당신을 존중한 거야
I respected you.
난 구식 남자야
I'm an old-fashioned guy.
난 사랑하는 사람을 애무하거나
거칠게 다뤄야 된다는 생각은 안 해봤어
I don't think that you should grope
and maul the one you love.
플로리다에 가기 전까지는
Until you get to Florida...
퐁텐블로 호텔에서
at the Fontainebleau...
담배 한 뭉치들고
들어가서 문 잠그고서 말야
with the door locked
and a carton of cigarettes.
우리 신혼여행 얘기잖아요
Red, our honeymoon.
위층으로 올라갑시다
Let's go upstairs.
싫어요, 영화보러 가요
No. Let's go to the movies.
결국 여기구나
Here we are.
그래
Yep.
난 아직도 이해가 안돼
So, I still can't believe...
켈소가 재키를 두고
팸 메이시랑 바람핀 거 말야
that Kelso cheated on Jackie
with Pam Macy.
그건 정말 너무 심한 행동이었어
I mean, that is just
a seriously uncool move.
맞아
Yeah.
그건 모든 걸 잃을 수도 있는 ...
I mean, to risk everything for...
에릭, 난 절대로 너한테
그런 짓 안 할게
Eric, I would never do that to you.
난 믿어도 돼
You can trust me.
정말?
Really?
정말이야
Absolutely.
난 절대로 체육관 뒤에서
팸 메이시랑 키스 안 할 거야
I would never kiss Pam Macy
behind the gym.
앞일은 모르는 거니까
절대란 말 하지마
Never say never, Donna.
이 밤도 결국 제대로 됐구나
This night turned out okay.
아주 낭만적이야
Pretty romantic.
그래, 딱 내가 상상했던 대로야
너 그리고 나..
Yeah, it's just how I imagined it.
Just you and me...
나 속이 너무 안 좋아
I do not feel too good.
고마워
Thank you.
어쩌면 내가 상상했던 대로는
아닐지도 모르겠다
Okay, maybe it's not just
how I imagined.
귀 막아
이 부분 굉장히 메슥거릴 거야
Cover your ears,
this part gets pretty gross.
번역수정: 김찬미 (husseyttl@nate)
최종수정: 김현정(fuchs@nate)
자유배포 / 수정금지
네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24
자유배포 / 수정금지
네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24